{
    "id": "1cdf19a9789d4bfeb8e723558518cc47",
    "title": "Formation of Questions",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "........................... James play cricket?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Does",
                "Do"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "2dace98d4dbc4934bcee9001c5f159e9"
        },
        {
            "question": ".................................... Alice speak French?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Does",
                "Do"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f6f453ea51714da3a1da8002719353a1"
        },
        {
            "question": "..................................... heat expand bodies?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Does",
                "Do"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ca2b36a34c874cb19854b1e34e60d74c"
        },
        {
            "question": "Does Peter .................................... models from clay?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "makes",
                "make"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3c0bbce096e64830ac0f8fd53698081f"
        },
        {
            "question": "Does she .................................... the violin each morning?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "practice",
                "practices"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1c77ea8a312b42779a96510b906c0d68"
        },
        {
            "question": "..................................... they play well yesterday?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Do",
                "Does",
                "Did"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "6939f9f2a63749f8aa11e7bbdde6550a"
        },
        {
            "question": "................................... he go to office by train?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Does",
                "Do"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a1906e2ac4e944d8bf0c851e08c7730a"
        },
        {
            "question": "..................................... the doctor coming to see her?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Is",
                "Has",
                "Does"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f9a1cd1d87f44f0faa858d91746a63dc"
        },
        {
            "question": "................................. the tablets bitter?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Were",
                "Was",
                "Have"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "464f12bf6dc042ce85a80c5a1b37948a"
        },
        {
            "question": "Will our boys ........................................ the match?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "win",
                "won"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e5a607f09a09402d947933ac39bdec44"
        },
        {
            "question": ".................................... Alice finished her homework?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Has",
                "Have"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "690c1b65dacd44b88c81d82a7cc31c80"
        },
        {
            "question": "Has he ............................... his exams well?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "did",
                "do",
                "done"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "a757b6fbd22a48d7800154cb75417877"
        }
    ]
}